# Skylar Harwell

## Accomplishments

As a Team Lead, I lead the TSO-FORMS team of 24 associates in day-to-day operations & training. I am responsible for implementing multiple process improvements to streamline work & increase efficiencies by updating & creating various SOPs, Process Maps, & Automated processes. I assist in agile team sprints to identify Future State processes & improvements by researching & reviewing process & procedures to ensure production efficiencies are gained.

#### **Technical Skills & Abilities**

- Word, Excel, Outlook, OneNote, SharePoint, Visio
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Github/Gitlab, Sequelize, JSON, RESTful APIs, Jest, Heroku
- Understanding of Agile Methodology

- Experienced in finding, creating, & updating SOP
- Proficient in cross-communication between departments & leading Enterprise initiatives virtually

## **Professional Experience**

# Services Coordinator - Administrative Services - Technical Services

08/24/2019 - Present

- Responsible for multiple Process Updates to maximize efficiency allowing team to not fill open positions & reduce staff from over 40 associates to the current 24 with no loss in production
- Tasked with creating Quality Assurance Review process to quantify individual's accuracy in production by creating metrics & Quality documents
- Worked with multiple Agile teams to research current & future state processes to analyze & implement improvements & provide recommendations to updates

#### **Technician** – Administrative Services – Technical Services

1/17/2018 - 08/23/2019

- Maintained production at a high level processing & approving multiple forms from Enterprise associates
- Multiple times was the top producer on the team often exceeding the average by double the next Technician

#### PIM Technician – Administrative Services – Document Services

09/26/2015 - 11/16/2018

- Executed a reorganization effort in Printing, Inserting, & Mailing (PIM) stock department to reallocate space & ensure organization of over 300 inserts & policy documents & removing over 150 unused items to maintain quality control & inventory
- Tasked with On-Boarding multiple technicians into the Cancellation process in PIM to reduce Overtime hours & increase quality handling of highly sensitive mail
- Responsible for analyzing & creating a notification process to phase out of a line of business that was expected to take over a week & was completed in less than a business day

## Claim Associate-Express - Property Claims

12/09/2013 - 09/25/2018

- Responsible for contacting & servicing claims under the Green demand pool
- Maintained productivity & consistently exceeded production & quality goals

## **Education**

**CPCU Designation** (In Progress)

Expected completion 2023

Georgia Tech (In Progress - December 2021)

Full Stack Developer Boot Camp

Valdosta State University December 2007

Bachelor of Arts

Abraham Baldwin Agricultural College June 2004

Associate of Arts

# **Completed Projects**

Movie Information app "GeorgiaScreen"

- A movie search app that takes the input of a movie title and provides info including Plot Summary, Actors, Directors, etc. and provides additional info about the actors with links to see where to stream these movies.
  - HTML & JavaScript
  - o **GeorgiaScreen**

#### Weather Generator App

- App that takes the name of a city and provides weather information for current and the next 5 days. App also saves your searches for quick reference.
  - o HTML & JavaScript
  - o Weather Generator

#### JavaScript Timed Quiz

- Fun little quiz about JavaScript that allows you to track a high score and compete with friends!
  - HTML & JavaScript
  - o Timed Quiz

& multiple other projects available via my portfolio

## **Outside of Work**

While not working I am an avid baker of all things from cookies, cakes & pies, to breads & pastries. I also spend my time working on sculpting & casting items & figures in resin & helping my wife with her art endeavors.